     My name is Saviour Emmanuel Edethu a newly admitted student of the BYU-Idaho to be precise, I am educationally inspired by the studies of Albert Einstein and Thomas Edison. The impact of education to a person’s life can not be over emphasized, because it will be revealed in the future state of the benefactor’s life just like Malcom X said  “Education is the passport of the future, for tomorrow belongs to those who prepare for it today”. 
     As a child my parents struggled to sponsor my primary school education and as such attending a university education at first was unthinkable of me and even though I dreamt on becoming a professional web developer, my parents had no means of helping me fulfill this dream due to financial challenges and the cost of tuition. My educational journey before now suffered a cool feet. I can recount being humiliated by my fellow pupil who had rich parents some years back when I was in my primary school, they mocked me on the grounds that I will never be successful later in life and I will not attend a university. After my primary education I was supposed to start my secondary school education immediately but was not opportune to continue until my hope was rekindled when I was introduced to BYU-Pathway by a friend. In the course of my learning at the BYU-Pathway connect I have attained an elevated height of transformation in my learning. Before I enrolled I hardly could gather the courage to address people, but BYU-Pathway through its gathering program has imbibe in me the ability to face crowds and address them on what ever issue provided I have a slight knowledge of the subject matter. Time management is a vital part of my learning in the BYU-Pathway as a result of that, I now manage time by setting goals and tying those goals to a time frame which makes me achieve maximum efficiency of time usage. My dream is to reckon a change to the world through Web development although my fear of achieving this dream, is owning a laptop. A laptop is very crucial to becoming a web developer as every tool he has to do is achieved through the use of his laptop. This sometimes sends a discouraging message to me because I do not have the financial means of acquiring a laptop. Nevertheless my attitude towards pursuing my education will not change because of my strong zeal and trust in Heavenly Father. I can also recount the most inspiring lesson I had learnt and applied in my life courtesy of the education I received from the BYU-Pathway, some month back on my PC103, we were taught “how to persevere” this lesson has helped me to persevere in many occasions when I try to give up especially when the tasks at hand seems so demanding and difficult to crack. 
     My educational journey defines me, reflecting backwards I am usually amazed at the level of transformation that has taken place in my life. For instance before my admission into BYU-Pathway, my phobia for mathematics was scary but now I can boast of solving basic arithmetic and algebraic mathematical problems. But I still anchor my hope on reaching the top of my education and serving my family and community with this skill.